Hello Sanjeev Dixit, let me tell you
where are you tracking the momentum, today you
see Mindtree's numbers are very good,
so short term money has moved into that, but it is still
think bank category and in that, whatever
you say about Bank Nifty,
whether it comes in 15 days or a month, but the
bank is in the front and in the media section, a lot of
commentary has come today, Bandhan
Bank and we are a Mandal Microfinance, they
say that landing is bad, recovery is
25 percent, finance chamber is invalid, 98%
management etc. diseases, recommend Vandana
etc. and shift to IDFC, you will be
rich, reported midcap bank, let me
give you an update of Rubaru circle, but 9350 has gone to
95 and a half, book profit in it and
making ₹2 handsome, you have two pieces, here
I would also say that for U Bank 1035,
I gave a target of 1150, it has become 1185, so
probably Micro Finance Law and Urban
Bank Khargone district level,
you  2 pictures if you say then I will start the
phone ji please clear the machine the topper will be
ICICI Lombard Insurance from the ground
and Insurance Guddu Yadav stream
ICICI Lombard operating 1658
character 215 34540 has a stoploss of 1510 12 this
is going back to see a little
Bahubali my favorite updates UP Bank of
Baroda Bank of Baroda will
give the highest record profit in this quarter which is yours
in July end episode 384 take that bus stop love
7250 digit ₹90 ok so Bank of Baroda
ambulance on this long reference but machine
probably today's hot topic of discussion across
innovation is of matches
what is your advice should you invest money should 7276
near it
see everything jhala whatever trend is there it is
telling friends and friends let's
everyone this parking rate price up function
birthday stock will make money over the next two
years to enquire  Into your window and
used to give you returns development in 10
minutes is the new is a no brainer as I told
you there is no metric of its valuation
before so it
is difficult for us to comment but I think you must have this in
your portfolio in small quantities,
on this very cautious opinion machine
snake is currently
seen taking Lal's opinion and on midcap IT, is there
any special reason that you are
seeing such tremendous momentum in midcap IT, so
ruling Russia's entry, we have
gone from very low, I still think the limit to Tech
Mahindra will give vote to develop is the Bank
of Baroda 140 so there I will get 430